HaxTalks Subs
Translations by MysteriousAura
Qiu Shan Jun and Xu You Rong will become husband and wife
Are there any objections?
Yes or no?
Does anyone have any objections?
I will ask one more time. Are there any objections?
Living all these seasons in the mountains, the wind and frost have dyed my clothes
From far away, the youth play
This red dust substance isn't like snow, it is like the moon
My clothes feel thin and cool, they mock and make me crazy
Asking what the meaning of my life is, or what I need to do
But the answer cannot be found in the books
Living a long life is hard
I hope I won't get lost along the way
Asking what the meaning of my life is, or what I need to do
But the answer cannot be found in the books
Living a long life is hard
I hope I won't get lost along the way
Way of Choices
Prisoner of Tong Palace
Wei Yang Palace
Orthodox Academy is here!
Mister?
You go in first
Okay
General
I thought that you wouldn’t come for the third night of Qing Tong Yan. Why did you?
I am a student of Orthodox Academy. Therefore, I have the right to attend Qing Tong Yan
That means you’re not planning on keeping the promise you’ve made
I plan on keeping my promise, but I don’t know if everyone else will be able to
Hmph. How naive
If you can keep your promise
And not cause a big disturbance at the wedding,
I am willing to spare your life
Wait a minute. The person who needs to keep his promise the most is you, General!
The marriage vow from before...
Is the true promise that you must keep
Mister, this thousand mile button will help you in your time of need
Is that..??
Hmph. Let's just say you got lucky this time
Thank you very much
You've awoken!
We meet again, Miss Mo Yu
I always thought that you were an intelligent person
You didn't attend the second night of Qing Tong Yan
So I was under the impression that you've already made your decision regarding Qing Tong Yan
That was probably the right choice
But, you showed up here again tonight
I'm a bit disappointed
I beg that you make the right decision which I know you're capable of
Forget about that marriage vow
Why?
In order to ensure stability
But this isn't fair!
Of course it isn't
There isn't a lot of fairness in this time and age, after all
Let's take your abilities into account
Comparing it to Xu You Rong or Qiu Shan Jun,
Is already not fair
In order to repel the demon clan, humanity needs to unite together
For this reason
No matter if the person is a court official, or representative from the south, they will all encourage the wedding between Qiu Shan Jun and Xu You Rong
For the benefit of society
You are too ignorant of that
If even you came
Then I will have to continue attending Qing Tong Yan
Is that so?
Please don't try to mess with my calculations. Just give up
You know, at first, I didn't even care about this marriage stuff
But because of your actions,
It keeps on reminding me
That I need a wife in the future
All of you are pressuring me
To slowly start caring about this matter
I don't like what all of you have tried doing to me before
If you want to use force,
Then I need to make your life miserable as well
Now that's fair!
Okay. Let's assume that's fair then
We'll see who will claim victory between the two of us
Tonight is your best opportunity to break up the marriage plans
Of course, you need to first be able to leave this place first
I suggest you think things over carefully
And wait for Qing Tong Yan to finish
Legends say that there was a dragon, buried deep underground. One day, it rose up into the sky, but no one knows where it went
Could this be the spell used to imprison the king in Nan Ke Ji at Tong Palace?
T/N: <> was a famous play written by Tang Xian Zu during the Ming Dynasty
No matter how strong the spell is, there is always a way out.
I just need to remember how each of these spells work
When they're changing, and when they're not
That will allow me the chance to escape
Here's the exit!
A dragon?
The imperial palace
Really does have a dragon!
What did you do to Chen Chang Sheng?
It looks like you already know the matters regarding Chen Chang Sheng
Please forgive me
I know that you did this to benefit us as a whole
Which is why you did this so reluctantly
However, Xu You Rong is a child who has her own opinions
Did you ask for her thoughts?
To marry the Dragon and the Phoenix together to ensure smooth sailing, that's a bit too boring
But that Chen Chang Sheng-
We simply can't stand on the sidelines and look on
I'm sure the others will make a decision that we find to be satisfactory
I understand, Empress
I will immediately go and help with the third night of Qing Tong Yan
Looks like Master was right
My luck really is the worst
He already said that fate is decided by the Heavens, and that there's no changing it
But I won't give up this easily
I will live with caution
I need to use xiu xing to change my fate before my twentieth birthday
That way, I will be able to have experiences past the age of twenty
That looks hard now. I will probably die right here
Thank you for not swallowing me in one bite
But I really want to continue living!
That probably sounds like a joke
Let me have one last battle with you!
No one can tell if they truly understand their situation. I can't tell, either
But I know how to read
I get it now...that last book was information on how to talk in dragon language
Ja!
I am here, ready to begin
We, the south, would like to thank the Empress for her warm welcome
Let everything be well today!
I will take this opportunity
On behalf of the Qiu Shan family, and Qiu Shan Jun himself, we would like to ask for approval of the marriage
Please serve as the witness to this
A message from the Empress herself:
Everyone should welcome this marriage
She also hopes that with the north and south united, we will be able to repel the demon clan
We also agree to this marriage
The Divine General also agrees to this, no objections here
Are all sides have no objections,
According to the rules, the next step is to plan the date
If there are no objections, the Qiu Shan Family and the Divine General can organize this
Marriage Book
Mister
Does anyone object to Qiu Shan Jun and Xu You Rong becoming husband and wife?
Although I know that you wish for me to stay here and talk with you
I cannot understand the dragon language that you are speaking
Also, there's a really important matter that I must attend to
I really need to go now
But I will definitely come back
Thank you so much
Last call
If there are no objections, Qiu Shan Jun and Xu You Rong's wedding will finally be settled
Are there any objections?
If that's the case...
I object!